import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Урок от 14го февраля',
  cards: [
    {
      question: 'especially',
      answer: 'особенно'
    },
    {
      question: 'age-mates',
      answer: 'ровесники'
    },
    {
      question: 'degree',
      answer: 'степень'
    },
    {
      question: 'to doubt',
      answer: 'сомневаться'
    },
    {
      question: 'once',
      answer: 'как только'
    },
    {
      question: 'adolescence',
      answer: 'юность/молодость/подростковый возраст'
    },
    {
      question: 'pressure',
      answer: 'давление'
    },
    {
      question: 'to lead',
      answer: 'приводить'
    },
    {
      question: 'to intend',
      answer: 'предназначать'
    },
    {
      question: 'reinforce',
      answer: 'усиливаться'
    },
    {
      question: 'let’s say',
      answer: 'допустим'
    },
    {
      question: 'stick to',
      answer: 'придерживаться'
    },
    {
      question: 'workforce',
      answer: 'рабочая сила/трудовые ресурсы'
    },
  ]
} as Category;
